

PROFILE

Boston-based UX/UI researcher and designer that excels at merging the practical with the delightful. I've loved creating things ever since I was a kid painting and coloring next to my dad. I was drawn to user experience design because of the ever changing nature of products, and the user needs that drive those changes. I create digital solutions to user problems through empathy, strategy and iteration.

EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Design Intern

Forrester • Boston, MA • August 2017 – Present

Conducting user research and utilize research to make informed design decisions. Creating high and low fidelity prototypes and testing prototypes to make iterative changes supported by user and business objectives.

• Forrester's Contact Us Page

Performed 1-on-1 user testing and ideated with Mgr. UX Design Designed a strategic plan, wireframes and prototype for testing

• Forrester's Search Page

Designed a Usability Research Test Plan and conducted Usability testing Synthesized research to inform iterative designs with Mgr, UX Design

Forrester's Mobile App

Designed a Usability Research Test Plan and conducted usability testing Synthesized research to inform future designs with team of 3

Program Manager

Forrester • Boston, MA • January 2016 - Present

Drive projects by defining scope and developing project plans, tracking milestones, ensuring deadlines are met, and facilitating internal and external expectations and communication.

EDUCATION

General Assembly

User Experience Design • New York City, NY • June 2018

User Experience Design Part-Time (UXD) is an accelerated design program to unpack design-thinking to solve user's needs. With a focus on next generation mobile/web applications in the digital space.

Suffolk University

Master of Public Administration - Business • Boston, MA • 2012 - 2013

University of Massachusetts - Lowell

Bachelor of Arts - Political Science • Lowell, MA • 2007 - 2012

CONTACT

drewkayla.com Drew.KaylaA@gmail.com 978 • 204 • 5521 in/kayladrew

SKILLS

User interviews
User Interface design
Affinity Mapping
Personas
Wireframing
Prototyping
Usability testing
Interface Architecture

TOOLS

Proficient

Sketch User Testing InVision Principle Axure RP Procreate

Intermediate

HTML5 Illustrator CSS3 Photoshop

Exploring

Zeplin InDesign